Hayim Raison

Volunteer - Be Ready Community Dev

Wilmington, DE - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Hayim-Raison/a1d2247e98d29e8b

Motivated problem-solver with six years of demonstrated ability to supervise, lead, follow and serve in all aspects of

operations, while also being responsible for the training of subordinate personnel.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front Desk Receptionist

US SECURITY ASSOCIATES - Wilmington, DE - March 2016 to Present

Volunteer

Be Ready Community Dev - 2013 to Present

Perform Jantorial duties and Monitor teenages doring trips/events.

- * Clean all windows, walls, sweep/mop floors and doors.
- * Ensure all entries and exits remain locked.
- * monitor computer usage in game room.

Lance Corporal

United States Marine Corps - 1999 to 2006

Engineer Equipment Electrical Systems Technician

United States Marine Corps - 1999 to 2006

Repaired electric motors, electronic modules, motor control circuits and electric power generation equipment. Troubleshot digital/logic components/circuits and made organizational and intermediate-level repairs on the electrical systems of engineer and general supply equipment. Diagnosed problems and made repairs following manuals and schematic diagrams.

Engineer Equipment Mechanic

United States Marine Corps - 1999 to 2003

Performed preventive maintenance and made repairs to diesel engines and gasoline- and diesel-driven construction

equipment including tractors, power shovels, road machinery, air compressors and concrete mixers.

EDUCATION

MILITARY SERVICE

Service Country: US Branch: US. Marines

Rank: E-3

July 1999 to July 2003

^{*} Basic equipment repairs

CERTIFICATIONS

Lifeguarding/First Aid/CPR/AED

May 2016 to May 2017

Delaware Security Guard

December 2015 to December 2020

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Personal Skills

 $Budget\ planning, Leadership,\ Microsoft\ Excel,\ Microsoft\ Word,\ Microsoft\ PowerPoint,\ Personnel\ management$